Tomer Noy Full Stack Developer

Petach Tikva | 054-885-9596 | tomernoy@outlook.com Github LinkedIn | tomernoy.com

SUMMARY

I'm an autodidact dedicated developer, experienced maily in Flutter, JavaScript and Python programming with background in computer science and some management skills.

I've lived in China for about 13 years so I'm also fluent in Chinese.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Python, Django, OOP, SQL, Javascript, Node.js, Dart, Flutter, Linux, MongoDB, AWS, REST APIs, HTML, CSS, SASS, HTMX, NGINX, Heroku, AliCloud.

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

DiamNet ** available on Google play and App store

A built from scratch full-stack cross-platform mobile app for the Diamond trading industry Written in Flutter

- Front-end: Dart/Flutter, HTML, CSS.
- Back-end: Linux Restful API using Node.js Express, MongoDB, NGINX, Websockets (live chats), reversed Proxies, load balancers, Alibaba Cloud (previously AWS and Azure), SMS auth, JWT, hashing, encryption algorithm, excel file uploads to app objects.

Jewelry Website

Jewelry shop website i created for my final project using Django, HTML/CSS, SQLight, HTMX and deployed on Heroku also available on Github

Kap & Roni

A version of the game "snakes and ladders" but based on reaction speed instead of luck Written in Flutter

- Moving players dynamically with Flutter Animations
- State management with providers

Interval Countdown Timer

Exercise interval countdown timer I built for my first 2 day Hackathon project - Preview HTML/CSS, JS

Temporary Email Generator

Desktop app that generates temporary emails for any registrations online quickly with a local inbox written in Python with Tkinter GUI

EXPERIENCE

Mobile Application Developer Xiamen, China DiamNet LTD - Building DiamNet** and uploading on Google play / App store 2016 - 2020

Office Manager Xiamen, China Julius Klein - Eliaz Diamonds 2012 - 2015

- Negotiating expensive diamond trade deals on international stock with high-end clients
- Handling logistics of products supply to stores across China safely

Translator Tel-Aviv, Israel Embassy Of China - Israel 2009 - 2011

Translating and handling confidential information regarding the consulate services in Israel

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development, Python and JavaScript program

10/2021 - Present

Tel-Aviv. Israel Developers Institute, TLV Coding Bootcamp

LANGUAGES

Hebrew - native speaker, English - fluent, Chinese - fluent